Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Minutes, 1933-1969
  - Industry Minutes, News, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Industry Minutes, Cashiers, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Industry Minutes, Direct Mail, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Industry Minutes, Dental, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Industry Minutes, General Office, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Industry Minutes, Finance, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Industry Minutes, Social Service, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Industry Minutes, Book, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Industry Minutes, Radio, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Industry Minutes, AWCAG, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Industry Minutes, Salesmen--Shoes, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Industry Minutes, Dry Goods, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Industry Minutes, Local 273, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Industry Minutes, FAECT & Local 1, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Corrugated Local Board Minutes, Jersey, NY, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Lumber Local Executive Board Minutes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Sample Card Local Executive Board Minutes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Dental Local Executive Board Minutes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - New Jersey Local Executive Board Minutes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Button--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Cosmetics--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Garment Supply Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Millinery--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Knitwear--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Retail--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Retail TV--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Textile--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--General Office--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Giftware--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Apparel--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Chemical & Paint--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Display--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Hardware--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Insurance--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Screen--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes--Shoe--Garment Group, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Garment Group--Button, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Garment Group--Garment Supply, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Garment Group--Knitwear, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Garment Group--Millinery, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Garment Group--Textile, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Garment Supplies--Garment, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Garment Supplies--Textile, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Garment Supplies--Knitwear, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Garment Supplies--Button, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Garment Supplies--Millinery, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Garment Supplis--Garment, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Garment Supplies--Textile, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Garment Supplies--Button, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Garment Supplies--Knitwear, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Garment Supplies--Millinery, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Garment Supplies--Button, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Garment Supplies--Garment, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Garment Supplies--Knit, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Garment Supplies--Millinery, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Garment Supplies--Textile, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Garment Supplies--Garment Supply, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Garment Supplies--Textile, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Garment Supplies--Millinery, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Garment Supplies--Button, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Garment Supplies--Knitwear, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Garment Supplies--Garment, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Garment Supplies--Textile, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Garment Supplies--Button, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Garment Supplies--Millinery, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Garment Supplies--Knitwear, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Garment Supplies--Garment, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Garment Group--Textile, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Garment Group--Button, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Garment Group--Millinery, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Garment Group--Knitwear, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Garment Group--Screen, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Garment Group--Garment, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Garment Group--Textile, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Garment Group--Millinery, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, Outside Salesmen, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, Outside Salesmen, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Wholesale Groups, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Salesmen Guild, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods Outside Salesmen, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Sales Guild, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Wholesale Groups, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods Outside Salesmen, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Sales Guild, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Retail TV, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, New Jersey, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Direct Mail, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Sales Guild, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Direct Mail I-III, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Sales Guild, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Wholesale Group, Local Executive Board Minutes, Toy & Gift, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 2, 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 13-19)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 3, 1954-1960 (Box 20, Folder 20-25)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 5, 1954-1961 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 6, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 1250, 1954-1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Department Store Locals, Local 1250B, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Local Minutes, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
  - Local Minutes, Corrugated, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Local Minutes, Retail Group, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, I-II, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Local Minutes, News, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Local Minutes, Corrugated, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Local Minutes, Retail Group, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Local Minutes, News, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Local Minutes, Corrugated, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, I-II, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 18-19)
  - Local Minutes, News, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Local Minutes, General Retail, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Local Minutes, Retail TV, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Local Minutes, Retail TV, Corrugated, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Local Minutes, Retail Group, General Retail, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Local Minutes, News, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Local Minutes, Corrugated, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Local Minutes, Retail Group, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Local Minutes, News, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Local Minutes, Corrugated, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Local Minutes, Retail Group, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Apparel, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 12-14)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cigar, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Food, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 16-18)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, NY, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, NY/Passaic, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, NY/Passaic/Metuchen, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, NY/Passaic, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Metal & Misc Processing, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Needle, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Sample Card, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Chemical & Paint, 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Dental, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Display, 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 16-18)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Finance, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, General Office, 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 2-5)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Insurance, 1957-1961 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, New Jersey, 1956-1961 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Screen, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Corrugated/Button, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Local Executive Board Minutes, Knitwear/Apparel, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Processing Group, Cigar, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Processing Group, Food, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Processing Group, Metal Misc., 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
  - Processing Group, Needle, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
  - Local Minutes, Cosmetic & Drug, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail I, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Local Minutes, Direct Mail, I & II, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Local Minutes, Sample Card, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Local Minutes, Apparel, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Local Minutes (corrugated), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Local Minutes, News, retail TV, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Local Minutes, Retail, Misc, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Local Board, Chain, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Local Board, corrugated, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Local Board, Cosmetic/Dental/Footwear/Dry Goods/Garment/Giftware/General Office & Book, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Local Board, Lumber/Misc Wholesale/Process/ Retail/ Textile, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Local Exec Bd, Chemical & Paint/Dental, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Local Exec Bd, Display/ Financial/ Insurance/ Screen, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Local Exec Bd, General Office, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Local Exec Bd, New Jersey, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Textile, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Button, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Millinery, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Knitwear, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Garment Supply, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - General Office, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Insurance/Display, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Screen, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Dental, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Local Board, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
  - Local Board & Membership Meeting, Apparel, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local Board & Membership Meeting, Sample Card, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Local Board & Membership Meeting, Cosmetic & Drug, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Local Board & Membership Meeting, Direct Mail, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Local Exec Board & Membership Meetings, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 12-20)
    General note
    In September 1963 District 65 shifted back to an area structure from a local structure. Area minutes are designated in the collected minutes of the Local Exec Board & Membership Meetings.
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1-9)
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 10-15)
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 16-18)
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Membership Meeting. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 5-9)
  - Membership Meetings, General Council. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files, 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Membership Meetings, Executive Council. Please see note on Box 26 for contents of Membership Meetings Files., 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Locals, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 12-14)
  - Direct Mail General Council, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Membership Minutes, Garment Center One, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Direct Mail Local Exec Board, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Direct Mail Local, Minutes of Exec Board, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Direct Mail Local Exec Board, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Direct Mail Local, Membership Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Series II: Counsel Files, 1940-1975
  - Closed AAA Cases, Miscellaneous, 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - Closed NLRB Cases, Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
  - A Betta Book Service, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - AAI Quilting Corp, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - A Millner Co., 1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - A Millner Co & Faclson Packing Co, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - A&B Upholstery Corp, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - A&S Electronic Die Corp, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Acadia Textile, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Accurate Lisk Letter Service, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Ace Drop Cloth Co, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Acme Refolding & Packing, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Acme Transfer & Storage Inc, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Action Letter Inc, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Adams Book Co, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Air Express International Corp, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Airex Radio Corp, 1963, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Alarm Device Mfg Co, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Alarm Device Mfg Co, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Alexander v NCDWA, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Allen Knitting Mills, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Wire Co Div of Loral Electronics, 1957-1967 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - AAA, Delinquent Accounts, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - American Bakeries Co. American Bakeries Co. Exhibits, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - American Bakeries Co. Exhibits, undated (Box not specified, Folder 7)
  - American Dictating Machine, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - American Direct Mail Co, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - American Discount Stores, 1962-1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - American Textile Import Co., 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Anderson Textile Refolding, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Apollo Sales, 1966-1968 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Approved Fabrics Corp, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Harold Aptaker, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Art Steel, 16489/70, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Art Steel, 2 CA 12327, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 17-18)
  - Art Steel, Application to Enforce Excelsior Subpoena, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
  - Art Steel, Index No 15675/70, I & II, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
  - Art Steel Co CB-CA Cases, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Art Steel Cases, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Art Steel Exhibit Copies, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Art Steel Payboard Application, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Art Supply Cases, I & II, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Association of Health, Welfare & Pension Plan Administrators, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Association of Uptown Converters, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Blowmolding Corp, 1962-1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Container Corp, 1966-1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Container Corp (bankruptcy), 1964-1969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Contaner Corp (briefs, opinions, transcripts), undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Container Corp (Court of Appeals), 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Container Corp (District Court), 1958, 19671968 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Augustin Davilla, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Automobile Club of NY, Challenges to 2d election, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Baker Brands, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Bako & Behnken vs Markowitz et al, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Baldwin Junction Lumber Corp, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Ballen Booksellers International, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Barnard College, 1970-1974 (Box 31, Folder 21-22)
  - Barnard College, Exhibits, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Barnard College, Resource Material, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Angel Barnecett, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Barnes & Nobel Bookstores, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Bartfeld Ribbons, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Belikoff Bros Inc., 1964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - People vs Bell & Colter, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Ben Kay Jewelry Corp, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Beth Israel Hospital, 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Co, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Bloch Winitz Co, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Blue Ridge Winkler Textiles, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Bluebird Knitwear Co, 1963, 1964, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Book Sales Inc, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Books et al requested, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Bridge Television Service Corp, 1951-1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - British Industries Employees Assoc, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Bruce Infant Products Corp, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Buckeye Cotton Oil, 1950-1952 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Burlington Mills, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Busch Kredit Jewelry Co, 1947, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Busch's Jewelry co., 1951 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Bush Trimming Co., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Credit Bureau Inc, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 24-28)
  - Carol Textile Inc, 1946-1963 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Center for Research Libraries, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Central Jersey Farmers Cooperative Assoc, 1965, 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Century Factors, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Century Oxford Mfg., 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Century Ribbon Mills Inc, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Certified Grocers, 1944-1964 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Charles Fisher & Sons, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Charles Wolton, 1965-1970 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - China Publications, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chromium Plating & Publishing Corp, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Clairol, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 12-17)
  - Clark O'Neil, 1962-1965 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Clay Adams, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Coin & Bernstein, 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Combining, 1960-1965 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Columbia Pictures Industries, 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Textile Slittng Co, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Comet Ray Letter Service, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Concord Fabrics, 1966-1971 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
  - Containair Systems Inc, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Continental Mailing & Folding, 1963-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Continental Trimming, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Corrugated Container Corp, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Cost of Living Council, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Cotton Processing Inc, 1961-1964 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Couleur Fabrics, 1967-1969 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Creiner & Brumberg, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Criminal Court File Arising out of May 3 Strike et seq., 1965 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Curry Contracting Corp / Zuckberg Co, 1960-1965 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - DCA Food Industries, 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - DPOWA (National), 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - D&C Textile Corp, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 18-19)
  - Darmon Tool & Mfg Corp & Durabilt Electronics, Arthur E. Carpenter, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Dauman Displays, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Davega Stores Inc, 1962-1969 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Davis Blass Co, 1961-1964 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Dayton Fabrics (Moses & Singer), 1968 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - DeNobili Cigar Co, 1948-1951 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Defender Industries, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 26)